<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>FocusMode Updates</title>
        <item>
            <title>Version 5.6.0</title>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 03:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>31</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>5.6.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <description><![CDATA[
<h1 id="focusmo-5.6.0">Focusmo 5.6.0</h1>
<h2 id="whats-new">What’s New</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Smart Logging System</strong>: Introducing logging, a new way to stay accountable and track your progress.
<ul>
<li>Add log anytime using global shortcut (cmd + ctrl + l), floating island or command panel</li>
<li>Bonus: Convert your logs into structured focus sessions for better analytics instantly from floating island or when creating a log</li>
</ul></li>
<li><strong>Redesigned Timeline</strong>: Timeline interface has been relocated and enhanced within the activity screen for a more intuitive experience</li>
<li><strong>Unified Activity Dashboard</strong>: A completely redesigned activity view that merges analytics and activity tracking into one comprehensive interface
<ul>
<li>Access detailed activity data for any day</li>
<li>Enhanced visualization with improved charts and data presentation</li>
<li>Rich insights and analytics to understand your productivity patterns</li>
<li>Seamlessly integrated logs within your timeline view</li>
</ul></li>
<li><strong>Daily Goal Screen</strong>: Beautiful chart display for tracking your daily focus goals and progress</li>
<li><strong>Floating Island Interface</strong>: Introducing a new sleek, minimal floating bar that provides quick access to logging and task creation without disrupting your workflow.
<ul>
<li>Bonus: You can write anything like a motivation quote or reminder to keep you focused</li>
</ul></li>
<li><strong>Calendar Events in Menubar</strong>: See upcoming events with countdown timer and notifications. Easily view and manage your calendar events directly from the menubar.</li>
<li><strong>Login using Google</strong>: No need to enter license to access your account, just login using your Google account. This creates base for future real-time sync.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="bug-fixes">Bug Fixes</h2>
<ul>
<li>Fixed skip button behavior in 1-minute warning - now correctly skips break instead of ending the entire session</li>
<li>Fixed: Not able to complete tasks when in paused state</li>
<li>Fixed: Activity duration calculation not accounting for overlaps and idle time</li>
<li>Fixed: Focus streak calculation</li>
</ul>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/auspy/focusmode-updates/releases/download/v5.6.0/focusmode_v5.6.0.zip"
                sparkle:edSignature="bR7CzlL2D+jz7P06rpJIU+L76wTnJKXrZmNqSG0rYgNPP2CJnIi9hvHiECJxi65ldDlnuCRfMECQxsPKwBKIBA=="
                length="20562977"
                type="application/octet-stream"/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
